Today this thing is being leaked all over the internet brothers,
you can steal someone's bag whether it is of fruit or juice by splitting
it in half and
look at this, he opens the packet of juice and does it again, I
always wanted to do this in my life
and let's experiment with it, brother,
I have also ordered this cell, let's see if
it reduces the amount or not, it
steals from others,
brother, maybe I think yes, it has its
own cell, brother, we will
put a cell, this will run on the shelf,
this cell will reduce on purchase,
and then we will do the juice, is it successful
or not, I have opened the cell,
but from here the mouth is
open, Aakash brother, reveal brother, it has been closed, close it,
what is it brother, look it has been closed,
open it again, it has been
opened now, do it
again, then the same can be done
with it,
I think it is water, Hasan
brother, take water, okay, the seller has done the
reduction on the cell, now it is on the cell packet,
brother, this is a juice bag, now let's see, can he split it in
half  Is it there or not and yes
and this juice should also be separate, this is
fine
and I will hold it from one side and then
move this sealer, first let's grind it a little,
press it like this, then it will not happen,
see this it is going
[Music]
rest see, I can see it, it is
visible to me, right,
I am doing it slowly, slowly,
I will do it slowly,
if you will come to know
[Music]
look that it has gone
bad brother, it has been sold from here, it has been
sold from here, look at this,
you should see this, it has been sold
brother, this is correct but it is not as correct
as it is being shown.